<resources>


    <!--    Start menu -->
    <string name="app_name">Computer Basics</string>
    <string name="start_menu">Learn Computer Basics\nFor Beginners</string>
    <string name="start_menu_description">it is start menu photo</string>

    <!--    Main Menu-->
    <string name="so">so</string>
    <string name="main_menu_text">Are you ready for \nthis journey ?</string>
    <string name="lets_start_text">Let\'s Start</string>
    <string name="main_menu_description">it is main menu photo</string>


    <!--    Choose menu-->
    <string name="choose_menu">Choose Menu</string>
    <string name="choose_img_description_1">it is hardware img</string>
    <string name="choose_img_description_2">it is software img</string>
    <string name="hardware_button_text">Hardware</string>
    <string name="software_button_text">Software</string>


    <!--    Hardware menu-->
    <string name="hardware_menu">Hardware Menu</string>
    <string name="internal_photo_description">it is internal photo</string>
    <string name="external_photo_description">it is external photo</string>
    <string name="external_text">External</string>
    <string name="internal_text">Internal</string>


    <!--    Internal menu-->
    <string name="external_menu">External Menu</string>
    <string name="motherboard_des">motherboard image</string>
    <string name="motherboard_text">The <b>motherboard</b> is the main circuit board of a computer that connects and allows communication between all components</string>
    <string name="next_button">Next</string>

    <string name="cpu_des">cpu image</string>
    <string name="cpu_text">The <b>CPU</b>  (Central Processing Unit) is the brain of the computer that processes instructions, performs calculations</string>

    <string name="hard_drive_des">hard drive image</string>
    <string name="hard_drive_text">A computer <b>hard drive </b>is a data storage device used to store and retrieve digital information. It can be either a Hard Disk Drive (HDD)</string>

    <string name="ram_des">ram image</string>
    <string name="ram_text"><b>RAM (Random Access Memory)</b> is a computer\'s short-term memory that temporarily stores data and instructions needed for running applications and processes.</string>

    <string name="ssd_des">ssd image</string>
    <string name="ssd_text"><b>SSD (Solid-State Drive)</b> is a storage device that uses flash memory to store data, providing faster read/write speeds compared to traditional hard drives (HDDs). </string>

    <string name="graphic_card_des">graphic card image</string>
    <string name="graphic_card_text"><b>A graphics card (GPU - Graphics Processing Unit)</b> is a hardware component in a computer responsible for rendering images, videos, and animations.</string>

    <string name="cooling_system_des">cooling system image</string>
    <string name="cooling_system_text">A computer <b>cooling system</b> is designed to prevent overheating by dissipating heat generated by components like the CPU and GPU</string>

    <string name="power_supply_des">power supply image</string>
    <string name="power_supply_text">A computer <b>power supply</b> converts electrical power from an outlet into usable power for the computer’s internal components.</string>

    <string name="dvd_drive_des">dvd drive image</string>
    <string name="dvd_drive_text">A computer <b>DVD drive</b> is an optical drive that reads and writes data to DVDs and CDs.</string>

    <!--    About Us-->
    <string name="about_us">About Us</string>


    <!--    External Menu-->
    <string name="internal_menu">Internal Menu</string>

    <string name="wireless_card_des">wireless card image</string>
    <string name="wireless_card_text">A computer <b>wireless card</b>, also known as a Wi-Fi card, is a hardware component that allows a computer to connect to wireless networks.</string>

    <string name="case_des">case image</string>
    <string name="case_text">A computer <b>case</b>, also known as a chassis or tower, is the enclosure that houses and protects the internal components of a computer</string>

    <string name="monitor_des">monitor image</string>
    <string name="monitor_text">A computer <b>monitor</b> is an output device that displays visual information from the computer.</string>

    <string name="mouse_des">mouse image</string>
    <string name="mouse_text">A computer <b>mouse</b> is an input device used to control the cursor on a computer screen.</string>

    <string name="keyboard_des">keyboard image</string>
    <string name="keyboard_text">A computer <b>keyboard</b> is an input device used to enter text, commands, and control functions into a computer.</string>

    <string name="speaker_des">speaker image</string>
    <string name="speaker_text">A computer <b>speaker </b>is an output device that produces audio from a computer.</string>

    <string name="webcam_des">webcam image</string>
    <string name="webcam_text">A computer <b>webcam</b> is an input device that captures video and images for purposes such as video conferencing, streaming, and online communication.</string>

    <string name="usb_hard_disk_des">usb hard disk image</string>
    <string name="usb_hard_disk_text">A computer <b>USB hard disk</b> is an external storage device that connects to a computer via a USB port. </string>

    <string name="joystick_des">joystick image</string>
    <string name="joystick_text">A <b>joystick</b> is an input device used to control movement in computer games and simulations.</string>


    <!--    Software Menu-->
    <string name="software_menu">Software Menu</string>


    <!--    monitor section-->
    <string name="monitor_menu_text">Monitor</string>
    <string name="monitor_img_1">this is monitor image 1</string>
    <string name="monitor_img_2">this is monitor image 2</string>
    <string name="monitor_img_3">this is monitor image 3</string>
    <string name="monitor_teach">A computer <b>monitor</b> is an electronic output device that displays visual information from a computer. It allows users to interact with their system by providing a graphical representation of applications, data, and media. The monitor serves as an interface between the user and the computer\'s processing unit.
    \n\n<b>Common Uses of Computer Monitors</b>
    \n1.  <b>General Use:</b> Web browsing, office work, education.
    \n2.  <b>Gaming:</b> High refresh rates and low response time for smooth gameplay.
    \n3.  <b>Graphic Design and Video Editing:</b> Color accuracy and high resolutions.
    \n4.  <b>Stock Trading:</b> Multiple monitor setups for tracking multiple charts.
    \n5.  <b>Programming:</b> Wide screens or dual monitors for coding efficiency.
    \n\nA computer <b>monitor</b> is an essential device that provides visual feedback to users. With various types, features, and use cases, choosing the right monitor depends on your specific needs, whether for work, gaming, or entertainment. \n\n</string>

    <!--    mouse section-->
    <string name="mouse_menu_text">Mouse</string>
    <string name="mouse_img_1">this is mouse image 1</string>
    <string name="mouse_img_2">this is mouse image 2</string>
    <string name="mouse_img_3">this is mouse image 3</string>
    <string name="mouse_teach">A computer <b>mouse</b> is a handheld input device used to control a computer\'s graphical user interface (GUI). It allows users to move a pointer (cursor) on the screen and perform actions such as selecting, dragging, and opening files or programs by clicking buttons on the mouse.\n\n
      <b>Functions of a Computer Mouse</b>
    \n The primary functions of a mouse include:
    \n <b>Pointing: </b>Moving the cursor to select items on the screen.
    \n <b>licking:</b>C Pressing buttons to open files, links, or execute commands.
    \n <b>Dragging and Dropping:</b> Moving files or objects from one place to another.
    \n <b>Scrolling:</b> Navigating through documents and web pages using the scroll wheel.
    \n <b>Right-Click Menu:</b> Accessing context menus for additional options.
    \n\nThe computer mouse is an essential input device for navigating and interacting with digital environments. Whether for general use, gaming, or professional applications, choosing the right mouse depends on factors like precision, ergonomics, and connectivity.\n\n</string>


    <!--    keyboard section-->
    <string name="keyboard_menu_text">Keyboard</string>
    <string name="keyboard_img_1">this is keyboard image 1</string>
    <string name="keyboard_img_2">this is keyboard image 2</string>
    <string name="keyboard_img_3">this is keyboard image 3</string>
    <string name="keyboard_teach">A computer keyboard is an input device that allows users to enter text, commands, and other data into a computer or similar device. It consists of a set of keys, each corresponding to letters, numbers, symbols, and function commands.
    \n\nA computer keyboard is an essential input device used for typing, controlling software, and improving productivity. Whether for general use, gaming, or professional applications, selecting the right keyboard depends on user needs and preferences.\n\n</string>


    <!--    speaker section-->
    <string name="speaker_menu_text">Sound Speaker</string>
    <string name="speaker_img_1">this is speaker image 1</string>
    <string name="speaker_img_2">this is speaker image 2</string>
    <string name="speaker_img_3">this is speaker image 3</string>
    <string name="speaker_teach">A computer speaker is an output device that converts electrical audio signals into sound, allowing users to listen to music, video audio, game sounds, and system notifications. It is an essential peripheral for both entertainment and productivity purposes.
    \n\n<b>Functions of Computer Speakers</b>
    \n\n1. <b>Audio Output:</b> Plays music, movies, video calls, and system sounds.
    \n2. <b>Gaming Experience:</b> Provides immersive sound effects in games.
    \n3. <b>Communication:</b> Enhances audio quality during online meetings and video calls.
    \n4. <b>Entertainment:</b> Supports streaming services and media playback with enhanced audio.
    \n5. <b>Audio Alerts:</b> Provides system notifications, error sounds, and alarms.
    \n\n Computer speakers enhance the audio experience by providing better sound quality for work, entertainment, and gaming. Depending on your needs, you can choose from budget options to high-end surround sound systems.\n\n</string>


    <!--    webcam section-->
    <string name="webcam_menu_text">WebCam</string>
    <string name="webcam_img_1">this is monitor image 1</string>
    <string name="webcam_img_2">this is monitor image 2</string>
    <string name="webcam_img_3">this is monitor image 3</string>
    <string name="webcam_teach">A webcam (short for "web camera") is a digital video camera that connects to a computer and is used for capturing live video and images. It enables users to conduct video calls, live stream, attend virtual meetings, and record videos. Webcams are commonly used in personal and professional settings such as remote work, online education, and content creation.
    \n\nCommon Webcam Connectivity Options
    \n1. <b>USB:</b> Most webcams connect via USB 2.0 or 3.0.
    \n2. <b>Wi-Fi/Bluetooth:</b> Wireless options allow placement flexibility.
    \n3. <b>Thunderbolt/USB-C:</b> High-speed connections for premium webcams.
    \nA webcam is an essential tool for communication, content creation, and surveillance. Whether for professional meetings, online learning, or streaming, selecting the right webcam depends on factors like resolution, frame rate, and additional features such as autofocus and low-light correction.\n\n</string>


    <!--    usb section-->
    <string name="usb_menu_text">Hard Disc</string>
    <string name="usb_img_1">this is usb image 1</string>
    <string name="usb_img_2">this is usb image 2</string>
    <string name="usb_img_3">this is usb image 3</string>
    <string name="usb_teach">A <b>USB hard disk</b>, also known as an external hard drive, is a portable storage device that connects to a computer via a USB (Universal Serial Bus) port. It allows users to store, back up, and transfer large amounts of data such as documents, videos, music, and software.
    \n\n\n A <b>USB hard disk</b> is an essential tool for storing and backing up data securely and conveniently. Whether you need a large capacity HDD for backups or a fast SSD for professional use, choosing the right drive depends on your needs and budget.\n\n</string>


    <!--    case section-->
    <string name="case_menu_text">Case</string>
    <string name="case_img_1">this is case image 1</string>
    <string name="case_img_2">this is case image 2</string>
    <string name="case_img_3">this is case image 3</string>
    <string name="case_teach">A computer case, also known as a PC chassis, tower, or enclosure, is the outer shell that houses and protects a computer\'s internal components, such as the motherboard, CPU, RAM, storage drives, and power supply. It provides structural support, cooling, and organization for these components while also contributing to the computer\'s aesthetics.
    \n\n <b>Common Computer Case Accessories</b>
    \n1. <b>RGB Fans:</b> Adds lighting and improves cooling.
    \n2. <b>Cable Extensions:</b> For better cable management and aesthetics.
    \n3. <b>Dust Filters:</b> Helps keep the interior clean.
    \n4. <b>Vertical GPU Mounts:</b> For showcasing graphics cards.
    \n5. <b>Fan Controllers:</b> Allows manual control over cooling.\n\n</string>


    <!--    joystick section-->
    <string name="joystick_menu_text">Joystick</string>
    <string name="joystick_img_1">this is joystick image 1</string>
    <string name="joystick_img_2">this is joystick image 2</string>
    <string name="joystick_img_3">this is joystick image 3</string>
    <string name="joystick_teach">A joystick is an input device used to control movement and actions in computer applications, primarily in gaming and flight simulations. It consists of a stick that pivots on a base and can be moved in multiple directions, often with buttons and triggers to perform additional functions.
    \n\n<b>Popular Joystick Brands</b>
    \nSome of the most popular joystick brands include:
    \n1. <b>Logitech:</b> Produces affordable gaming joysticks with good features.
    \n2. <b>Thrustmaster:</b> Known for high-quality flight and racing simulation peripherals.
    \n3. <b>Saitek:</b> Offers professional-grade flight and space simulation controllers.
    \n4. <b>Hori:</b> Specializes in arcade-style joysticks for fighting games.
    \n5. <b>Razer:</b> High-end gaming joysticks with premium build quality.\n\n</string>

    <!--wireless Wifi-->
    <string name="wifi_menu_text">Wireless Wifi</string>
    <string name="wifi_img_1">this is wifi image 1</string>
    <string name="wifi_img_2">this is wifi image 2</string>
    <string name="wifi_img_3">this is wifi image 3</string>
    <string name="wifi_teach">Wi-Fi (Wireless Fidelity) is a technology that allows computers and other devices to connect to the internet or communicate with each other wirelessly using radio waves. It eliminates the need for physical cables, providing flexibility and convenience for accessing networks in homes, offices, and public spaces.
    \n\nWi-Fi is an essential technology for modern computing, offering convenience and flexibility for accessing the internet. Choosing the right Wi-Fi setup involves considering speed, range, security, and compatibility with your devices.\n\n</string>


    <!--    motherboard section-->
    <string name="motherboard_menu_text">Motherboard</string>
    <string name="motherboard_img_1">this is motherboard image 1</string>
    <string name="motherboard_img_2">this is motherboard image 2</string>
    <string name="motherboard_img_3">this is motherboard image 3</string>
    <string name="motherboard_teach">A motherboard is the main circuit board in a computer that connects and allows communication between all the hardware components such as the CPU, RAM, storage drives, GPU, and peripherals. It acts as the central hub that facilitates data transfer and power distribution across the system.
    \n\n<b>Popular Motherboard Brands</b>
    \n1. <b>ASUS:</b> Known for high-end features and durability.
    \n2. <b>MSI:</b> Offers good performance and overclocking features.
    \n3. <b>Gigabyte:</b> Reliable motherboards with excellent cooling solutions.
    \n4. <b>ASRock:</b> Affordable and feature-packed options.
    \n5. <b>EVGA:</b> High-performance boards, primarily for gaming.\n\n</string>

    <!--    CPU section-->
    <string name="cpu_menu_text">Central Processing Unit</string>
    <string name="cpu_img_1">this is cpu image 1</string>
    <string name="cpu_img_2">this is cpu image 2</string>
    <string name="cpu_img_3">this is cpu image 3</string>
    <string name="cpu_teach">The Central Processing Unit (CPU), often referred to as the "brain" of the computer, is the primary component that executes instructions and processes data. It performs calculations, logic operations, and manages data flow between different components, allowing the system to run applications and perform tasks.
        \n\n<b>Popular CPU Brands and Models</b>
\nTwo major companies dominate the CPU market:
    \n<b>Intel:</b>
    \nPopular CPU series:
    \n<b>Core i3:</b> Entry-level, basic computing tasks.
    \n<b>Core i5:</b> Mid-range, suitable for gaming and multitasking.
    \n<b>Core i7:</b> High-performance computing.
    \n<b>Core i9:</b> Enthusiast-grade for gaming and productivity.
    \n<b>Xeon:</b> Used for server and workstation environments.
    \n\n<b>AMD:</b>
    \nPopular CPU series:
    \n<b>Ryzen 3:</b> Entry-level tasks.
    \n<b>Ryzen 5:</b> Mid-range for gaming and productivity.
    \n<b>Ryzen 7:</b> High-performance applications.
    \n<b>Ryzen 9:</b> Extreme workloads and gaming.
    \n<b>EPYC:</b> Enterprise and server-level CPUs.\n\n</string>


    <!--    hard drive section-->
    <string name="hard_drive_menu_text">Hard Disk Drive (HDD)</string>
    <string name="hard_drive_img_1">this is hard drive image 1</string>
    <string name="hard_drive_img_2">this is hard drive image 2</string>
    <string name="hard_drive_img_3">this is hard drive image 3</string>
    <string name="hard_drive_teach">A Hard Disk Drive (HDD) is a traditional data storage device used in computers and other electronic systems to store operating systems, applications, files, and multimedia. HDDs use magnetic storage and spinning platters to read and write data, making them suitable for storing large amounts of information at an affordable cost.
    \n\nHard drives are an essential component for storing data, providing affordable solutions for backups, gaming, and everyday use. While SSDs are faster, HDDs remain valuable for users needing large storage at lower costs.\n\n</string>


    <!--    RAM section-->
    <string name="ram_menu_text">RAM (Random Access Memory)</string>
    <string name="ram_img_1">this is ram image 1</string>
    <string name="ram_img_2">this is ram image 2</string>
    <string name="ram_img_3">this is ram image 3</string>
    <string name="ram_teach">Random Access Memory (RAM) is a type of volatile memory that temporarily stores data and instructions for the CPU while a computer is running. It provides high-speed access to data, making applications and processes run faster compared to accessing data from storage devices like HDDs or SSDs.
    \n\n<b>Popular RAM Brands</b>
    \nSome reliable RAM manufacturers include:
    \n1. Corsair.
    \n2. G.Skill.
    \n3. Kingston.
    \n4. Crucial.
    \n5. TeamGroup.\n\n</string>


    <!--    SSD section-->
    <string name="ssd_menu_text">SSD (Solid State Drive)</string>
    <string name="ssd_img_1">this is ssd image 1</string>
    <string name="ssd_img_2">this is ssd image 2</string>
    <string name="ssd_img_3">this is ssd image 3</string>
    <string name="ssd_teach">A Solid State Drive (SSD) is a high-speed storage device that uses flash memory to store data. Unlike traditional Hard Disk Drives (HDDs), SSDs have no moving parts, making them faster, more durable, and energy-efficient. They are commonly used in laptops, desktops, gaming consoles, and enterprise servers for their superior speed and reliability.
    \n\n<b>Popular SSD Brands</b>
    \nSome reliable brands that manufacture high-quality SSDs include:
    \n1. <b>Samsung:</b> 970 EVO, 980 Pro (popular NVMe options).
    \n2. <b>Western Digital (WD):</b> WD Blue, WD Black series.
    \n3. <b>Crucial:</b> MX500 (SATA) and P5 (NVMe) series.
    \n4. <b>Kingston:</b> A2000, KC2500 series.
    \n5. <b>Seagate:</b> FireCuda (for gaming), Barracuda SSDs.
    \n6. <b>ADATA:</b> XPG series for gaming.\n\n</string>


    <!--    Graphic card-->
    <string name="graphic_card_menu_text">Graphics Card (GPU)</string>
    <string name="graphic_card_img_1">this is graphic card image 1</string>
    <string name="graphic_card_img_2">this is graphic card image 2</string>
    <string name="graphic_card_img_3">this is graphic card image 3</string>
    <string name="graphic_card_teach">A Graphics Processing Unit (GPU), commonly known as a graphics card, is a hardware component that processes and renders images, videos, and animations. It offloads graphical processing from the CPU, improving performance in tasks such as gaming, video editing, 3D rendering, and AI workloads.
    \n\nPopular Graphics Card Models (2025)
    \n  NVIDIA: RTX 4090, RTX 4080, RTX 4070 Ti, RTX 4060 Ti.
    \n\n  AMD: RX 7900 XTX, RX 7800 XT, RX 7600 XT\n\n</string>


    <!--    DVD drive-->
    <string name="dvd_menu_text">Digital Versatile Disc drive</string>
    <string name="dvd_img_1">this is dvd image 1</string>
    <string name="dvd_img_2">this is dvd image 2</string>
    <string name="dvd_img_3">this is dvd image 3</string>
    <string name="dvd_teach">A DVD drive (Digital Versatile Disc drive) is an optical disc drive that allows a computer to read and write data to DVDs and CDs. It is used for installing software, watching movies, burning data, and backing up files.
    \n\n<b>Internal DVD Drives:</b>
    \n1.  Installed inside a desktop or laptop computer.
    \nConnects via SATA or older IDE interfaces.
    \nTypically found in tower PCs.
    \n\n2.  External DVD Drives:
    \nPortable drives that connect via USB.
    \nIdeal for laptops and ultrabooks without built-in drives.
    \nPlug-and-play functionality.
    \n\nDVD drives remain a useful tool for archiving data, installing software, and media playback, even as newer technologies emerge. External DVD drives are a great option for users with modern laptops lacking an optical drive, while internal drives are still popular in desktop builds.\n\n</string>


    <!--    Power Supply-->
    <string name="power_text">Computer Power Supply (PSU)</string>
    <string name="power_img_1">this is power supply image 1</string>
    <string name="power_img_2">this is power supply image 2</string>
    <string name="power_img_3">this is power supply image 3</string>
    <string name="power_teach">A Power Supply Unit (PSU) is a hardware component that converts electrical power from an outlet (AC) into usable power (DC) for a computer\'s internal components such as the motherboard, CPU, GPU, storage drives, and cooling systems. It ensures stable and efficient power delivery to maintain system stability and performance.
    \n\nA reliable power supply is crucial for system stability and longevity. Choosing the right PSU ensures efficient power delivery, reduces energy waste, and protects your components from electrical damage. Whether building a gaming PC or a high-end workstation, investing in a quality PSU is essential.
\n\n</string>


    <!--    Cooling system-->
    <string name="cooling_menu_text">Cooling System</string>
    <string name="colling_img_1">this is colling image 1</string>
    <string name="colling_img_2">this is colling image 2</string>
    <string name="colling_img_3">this is collingimage 3</string>
    <string name="colling_teach">A computer cooling system is a set of components designed to dissipate heat generated by the CPU, GPU, and other internal hardware to maintain optimal operating temperatures and prevent overheating. Proper cooling enhances system stability, longevity, and performance.
    \n\n<b>Popular Cooling Brands</b>
    \nSome of the leading brands that manufacture cooling solutions include:
    \n1.  Noctua.
    \n2.  Corsair.
    \n3.  Cooler Master.
    \n4.  NZXT.
    \n5.  Thermaltake.
    \n6.  Be Quiet!.
    \n\n</string>

    <!--    Software menu-->
    <string name="software_def">Definition of Computer Software</string>
    <string name="system_software_def">System Software</string>
    <string name="application_def">Application Software</string>
    <string name="programming_def">Programming Software</string>
    <string name="function_software_def">Functions of Software</string>
    <string name="software_hardware_def">Software vs Hardware</string>
    <string name="example_software_def">Examples of Popular Software</string>

    <!--    About Us menu-->
    <string name="about_us_text_1">Welcome to <b>Computer Basics for Beginners</b>, your go-to learning resource for understanding the fundamentals of computer hardware and software. Whether you\'re a beginner looking to expand your knowledge or someone seeking to refresh your skills, our app provides interactive and engaging content to help you master the basics.
        \n\n<b>What We Offer</b>
    \n\n<b>Hardware Basics</b>:
    \nLearn about the essential components of a computer, including the CPU, RAM, storage devices, and peripherals.
        \n\n<b>Software Fundamentals:</b>
    \nExplore operating systems, applications, and tools essential for everyday computing.
        \n\n<b>Our Mission</b>
    \nOur mission is to make learning computer basics easy and accessible for everyone. Whether you\'re a student, a professional, or just curious about technology, our goal is to provide you with the knowledge and confidence to navigate the digital world.
        \n\n<b>Contact Us</b>
    \nIf you have any questions, suggestions, or feedback, feel free to reach out to us:
        \n<b>Follow us on social media:</b> <a href="https://www.instagram.com/its_bwn.03/">Instagram</a>, <a href="https://x.com/vepa_vagyok">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/vepa-babayev-273b22330/">Linkedin</a>, <a href="https://github.com/Vepa03">GitHub</a>.</string>
    <string name="about_us_text_2"><b>Email:</b> <a href="to_gmail_menu">help_us.@gmail.com\n\n\n</a></string>

    <string name="need_help">Send Email</string>

    <!--    Gmail menu-->
    <string name="send_us_email">Send Us Email</string>
    <string name="send_button_text">SEND</string>
    <string name="gmail_name">program.pilot.03@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="subject_name">Subject ...</string>
    <string name="compose_email">Compose email ...</string>

<!--    definition software-->
    <string name="def_software_tool">Definition of Computer Software</string>
    <string name="def_software_text">Computer software refers to a collection of instructions, data, and programs that enable a computer to perform specific tasks and functions. Unlike hardware, which is the physical component of a computer, software is intangible and serves as the interface between the user and the machine, allowing users to interact with the hardware and perform various operations.
    \n\n<b>Computer software can be categorized into three main types:</b>
    \n1. System Software
    \n2. Application Software
    \n3. Programming Software
    \n\nComputer software is an essential part of modern technology, enabling computers to perform useful tasks. From operating systems to application software, it plays a crucial role in everyday life, businesses, and industries.\n\n</string>


    <!--    system software-->
    <string name="system_software_tool">System Software</string>
    <string name="system_software_text">System software is a type of computer software designed to manage and control hardware components, provide a platform for running application software, and facilitate the interaction between users and hardware. It acts as an intermediary between hardware and end-user applications, ensuring the system operates efficiently.
    \n\n<b>System software can be categorized into the following types:</b>
    \n1. Operating System (OS).
    \n2. Utility Software.
    \n3. Device Drivers.
    \n4. Firmware.
    \n5. Programming Language Translators.
    \n\nSystem software is essential for the smooth functioning of a computer. It acts as a foundation for application software and ensures efficient interaction with hardware components. Whether it\'s an operating system, utility software, or drivers, system software plays a crucial role in computing environments.\n\n</string>

    <!--    application software-->
    <string name="application_software_tool">Application Software</string>
    <string name="application_software_text">Application software refers to programs or applications designed to help users perform specific tasks or functions on a computer or mobile device. Unlike system software, which manages hardware and system operations, application software provides tools to enhance productivity, entertainment, and communication.
    \n\n<b>Types of Application Software</b>
    \nApplication software can be broadly classified into several categories based on its purpose and function:
    \n1. General-Purpose Software.
    \n2. Specialized Software.
    \n3. Web-Based Applications (Cloud Software).
    \n4. Business and Productivity Applications.
    \n5. Entertainment and Multimedia Software.
    \n6. Utility Software.
    \n7. Mobile Applications.
    \n\nApplication software plays a crucial role in modern computing by allowing users to perform specific tasks efficiently. Whether it’s for work, entertainment, or communication, application software enhances productivity and simplifies complex processes.\n\n</string>

    <!--    programming software-->
    <string name="programming_software_tool">Programming Software</string>
    <string name="programming_software_text">Programming software refers to tools that developers use to write, edit, test, debug, and maintain code for creating applications, websites, and system software. These tools help programmers translate human-readable code into machine-executable instructions.
    \n\n<b>Types of Programming Software</b>
    \nProgramming software is categorized into several types based on functionality and purpose:
    \n1. Text Editors.
    \n2. Integrated Development Environments (IDEs).
    \n3. Compilers.
    \n4. Debuggers.
    \n5. Version Control Systems (VCS).
    \n6. Build Automation Tools.
    \n7. API Development and Testing Tools.
    \n8. Database Management Tools.
    \n\nProgramming software plays a crucial role in modern software development, offering tools for writing, testing, debugging, and deploying applications efficiently. Whether you\'re a beginner or a professional developer, choosing the right programming software can enhance productivity and streamline the development process.\n\n</string>


    <!--    functions software-->
    <string name="function_software_tool">Functions of Software</string>
    <string name="function_software_text">Software plays a crucial role in modern computing by providing instructions to hardware and enabling users to perform various tasks efficiently. The functions of software can be categorized based on its type and purpose. Here are the key functions of software:
    \n\n1. System Management Functions.
    \n2. Application-Oriented Functions.
    \n3. Software Development Functions.
    \n4. Business and Enterprise Functions.
    \n5. Scientific and Engineering Functions.
    \n6. Security and Maintenance Functions.
    \n7. Educational Functions.
    \n8. Entertainment and Media Functions.
    \n\nSoftware serves a variety of functions depending on its type and purpose. Whether it\’s managing hardware, assisting in business operations, or enhancing user productivity, software plays an essential role in modern technology.\n\n</string>


    <!--    software vs hardware-->
    <string name="software_hardware_tool">Software vs Hardware</string>
    <string name="software_hardware_text">Hardware and software are the two fundamental components of a computer system that work together to perform tasks and operations. While hardware refers to the physical components, software consists of the set of instructions that tell the hardware what to do.
    \n\nHardware and software are the core components of any computer system. Hardware provides the foundation, while software enables functionality. Both are essential for the smooth operation of modern devices and technology.\n\n</string>

    <!--    example software-->
    <string name="example_software_tool">Examples of Software</string>
    <string name="example_software_text"><b>Examples of Popular Software Across Different Categories</b>
    \nHere are some widely used software applications categorized based on their functionality and purpose.
    \n1. System Software.
    \n2. Application Software.
    \n3. Programming Software.
    \n4. Database Management Software.
    \n5. Security Software.
    \n6. Gaming Software.
    \n7. Business and Finance Software.
    \n8. Educational Software.
    \n9. Cloud Storage Services.
    \n10. Operating System-Based Software.
    \n\nPopular software applications are designed to meet different needs, from personal productivity to business operations. The right software can help users achieve their goals more efficiently and enhance their computing experience.\n\n\n</string>
</resources>